https://www.life-answers.com/privacy.aspx

by Jill Saint JamesPrivacy Page
The information and data contained on and through the Numerogy areas of the Life-Answers.com Web site is to be treated purely for your
entertainment purposes only. Any prediction or other message that you receive is not a substitute for advice, programs, or treatment that you would
normally receive from a licensed professional such as a lawyer, doctor, psychiatrist, or financial advisor. Accordingly, Life-Answers.com provides
no guarantees, implied warranties, or assurances of any kind, and will not be responsible for any interpretation made or use by the recipient of the
information and data mentioned above.
Privacy Statement
Privacy Policy
Welcome to Life-Answers.com - the number one site in the world for Numerology. We are happy to provide services to you based on the following conditions.
Privacy
Please read over this Privacy Policy, which also governs your visit to Life-Answers.com.
At Life-Answers.com, one of our top priorities is making sure that the information we have about you is protected and secure.
We value our relationship with you and work hard to preserve your privacy. We do collect personal information to allow us to personalize
Horoscopes, Numerology and Numerology reports. We regard all personal information - including birth data - as completely confidential, and will
not divulge your information to any third party.
Information Collection & Use
In order to receive any free or paid reports, daily forecast or other products we provide, you must first complete an order form. When
ordering you will need to make certain entries (such as name, birth date and email address) so we can contact you about periodic updates on various
matters in which you've expressed an interest, like: events that may impact your life, exclusive opportunities, referrals, and discounts on materials
that will help you make the most out of your life.
Life-Answers.com is the sole owner of the information collected on Life-Answers.com.
If you purchase a product or service from Life-Answers.com, you will need to fill in certain personal information on your order form.
You will need to fill in contact entries (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial entries (such as credit card number, expiration date.)
Life-Answers.com uses these items for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If there is any problem in processing an order, Life-Answers.com
will contact you.Use of EntriesThe entries you fill out on your order forms are used to calculate your Numerology
report and/or to provide you with a daily forecast that is personally relevant to you because it is specifically based on your birth information.
The entries are also used to identify upcoming events and subjects that may interest or affect you, so we can let you know about them and any
opportunities or actions you can take to make the most of conditions and chances to improve your life.
Communications from
Life-Answers.com
Special Offers and UpdatesWe will occasionally send you information on exclusive opportunities, referrals, and discounts
on materials that will help you make the most of the current conditions as they arise.
You can always choose not to receive these types of communications. See 'Choice/Opt-out' below.
Customer ServiceBased upon the entries you provide in the forecast registration and order forms, Life-Answers.com may
send you a confirmation email to verify your order. Life-Answers.com will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the
services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you only via email.
Profile
Life-Answers.com stores the material collected through order forms, log files and third party sources to create a "profile" of your
preferences. Life-Answers.com ties your personal entries and your purchasing history to the profile, in order to provide opportunities, updates,
offers tailored specifically to fulfill your individual needs and to improve the content of your daily Forecast, other email updates, and the
resources presented on Life-Answers.com.
Life-Answers.com does not share your profile with other third parties.
Agents
Life-Answers.com uses a credit card processing company and/or PayPal to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain,
share, store or use personally identifiable entries and materials for any other purpose.
Legal Disclaimer
Life-Answers.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable entries and materials as required by law and when
Life-Answers.com believes that disclosure is necessary to protect its rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.
Choice/Opt-out
If you no longer wish to receive your daily Forecast or exclusive opportunities for offers and discounts or important updates and how they'll
affect you, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each forecast or email or here Contact Us link.
Other FilesLife-Answers.com gathers certain data automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes
internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp.
Life-Answers.com uses this data, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer Life-Answers.com, to track users’
movements around the site and to gather demographic information about subscribers as a whole.Life-Answers.com does link this
automatically-collected data to personally identifiable entries in order to determine your country of residence for customs and shipping purposes.
Cookies
Life-Answers.com does not use cookies on its site except for your daily forecast which is on our home page and only when you have opted to use this
feature. This allows us to provide you with your daily forecast each day without you having to re-input your information.
Links to Other SitesThis Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Life-Answers.com .
Please be aware that Life-Answers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information
collected by Life-Answers.com.
Access to Personal Information
If your personally identifiable entries change, or if you no longer desire your daily Forecast or emails about opportunities, updates,
offers tailored specifically to fulfill your individual needs, you may correct, update, delete or unsubscribe.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on any order forms,
the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).
Life-Answers.com follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal entries you provide, both during transmission and once
Life-Answers.com receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while
Life-Answers.com strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal entries, Life-Answers.com cannot guarantee its absolute security.
If you have any questions about security on this Web site, you can email us here Contact Us
Changes to this Privacy Statement
If Life-Answers.com changes this privacy policy, Life-Answers.com will post those changes to this privacy statement. Life-Answers.com reserves the
right to modify this privacy statement at any time.
Children's Privacy
Our Company Commitment to Children's Privacy: Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's
Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen years or older.
YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS
THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN THE CHILD
ONLINE PRIVACY ACT (COPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.
LATEST UPDATE
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: July 4, 2020. Contact Us If you have any questions or concerns that you feel weren’t addressed herein,
please contact us here Contact Us
All Rights Reserved.This Website and all of its contents are protected by copyright laws and/or trademarks or other laws.
No part may be reproduced, stored in a retrieval system, or transmitted in any form or by any means, electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or
otherwise, without the written permission of Life-Answers.com.
This Terms & Conditions Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between You and us and governs your use of the Service, superseding
any prior agreements between You and us with respect to the Service.
